







Last Active: 18-Jan-21 Last Modified: 18-Jan-21

Jump to Section

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills |

## Summary

Experienced in working on Waterfall and Agile SCRUM and KANBAN methodologies.

Extensive knowledge about STLC & SDLC

My SQL server.

Creating User stories using JIRA

Proficient in using Microsoft Office MS Word, Excel, Power point, Access.

## Work Experience

Allianz Technology as Business Analyst

Aug 2020 to Till Date

- \* Work with various stakeholders to Gather, Understand and analyze their requirements.
- \* Creating User Stories, Business Requirement Document (BRD), Functional Requirement Document (FRD), Use Cases & Work Flow models.
- \* Providing Demo/Presentation sessions to the clients.
- Assist in UAT Testing.
- \* Getting changes approved from client by raising Project change request forms. Handling the change requests efficiently & effectively.
- \* Disseminate the requirements within the Development Team.
- \* Assisting Testers in creation of Test Cases.
- \* Create basic test scenarios to be used in testing the business applications in order to verify that client requirements are incorporated into the system design.
- \* Analyzing test results in various phases i.e. Development, QAT & Staging.
- \* Assisting in Technical review to verify 'intent of change' is carried through phase of project as per client's requirement.
- \* End to End product delivery.
- DXC Technology as Associate Professional Business Analyst May 2017 to Mar 2020

Project - POINT IN - Insurance Policy Administration Software for all Line of Businesses.

#### Roles & Responsibilities:

- \* Work with various stakeholders to Gather, Understand and analyze their requirements.
- \* Creating User Stories, Business Requirement Document (BRD), Functional Requirement Document (FRD), Use Cases & Work Flow models.
- \* Providing Demo/Presentation sessions to the clients.
- \* Assist in UAT Testing.
- \* Cetting changes approved from client by raising Project change request forms. Handling the change requests efficiently & effectively.

# **Important**

 Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld.

- Disseminate the requirements within the Development Team.
- Assisting Testers in creation of Test Cases
- Create basic test scenarios to be used in testing the business applications in order to verify that client requirements are incorporated into the system design.
- Analyzing test results in various phases i.e. Development, QAT & Staging.
  Assisting in Technical review to verify 'intent of change' is carried through phase of project as per client's requirement.
- End to End product delivery
- Lead the Implementation of Automation processes/solutions into the Project.

Project - User Life-Cycle Management for Swiss Reinsurance Pvt Ltd

#### Roles & Responsibilities:

- Incident Management for SwissRe Active Directory.
- Role Matrix maintenance as per business requirement.
- Access provisioning per the Role Matrix
- Process Automation.

### Xceedance Infotech Pvt Ltd as Analyst

Jan 2016 to Feb 2017

## Roles & Responsibilities:

- End to End Product delivery.
- Requirement gathering and understanding client's requirement.
- Conceptional Test plan creation including positive, negative & regression testing.
- Raising requests to create Incidents (Tickets) to track the issue.
- Demonstrating the requirements to the technical team.
- Functional Testing User Acceptance testing (UAT) & Quality Analysis testing (QAT) after change implementation before delivering the changes
- Coordinated with clients for feedback on changes implemented and tracked the changes for client's complete satisfaction

#### VFS Global Services Pvt Ltd. as Officer

Feb 2014 to Dec 2015

## Roles & Responsibilities:

- Sold Travel Insurance to applicants and managed travel insurance related queries.
- Processed applications for work, Student, Tourist and Seaman Visas.
- Assessed and decided on all types of immigration applications for permits and visas.
- Assisted Visa Officers at embassy in resolution of various visa application related issues.
- Specialize in expediting paperwork whilst ensuring adherence to applicable laws and regulations.
- Advised applicants on all immigration laws, policy and procedures as per the embassy guidelines.
- Informed applicants of any issues with their visa applications.
- Created and maintained ad hoc reports.

^ Back to Top

#### **Education**

UG: B.Sc (Maths) from Delhi University - Other in 2012

PG: in 0

^ Back to Top

## IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used Experience
Word, Excel, Power Point, Access	
JIRA, Sql Server	

^ Back to Top

## Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English	Expert	✓	✓	✓
Hindi	Expert	✓	✓	✓
Punjabi	Beginner	✓	✓	✓

^ Back to Top

#### **Affirmative Action**

#### **Work Authorization**

Physically Challenged: No

Job Type: Permanent Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.